<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle">
    <channel>
        <title>Audia Changelog</title>
        <link>https://github.com/Bibhav48/audia-dist</link>
        <description>Audia updates</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title>0.2.0</title>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 02:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>9</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>0.2.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>14.4</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[
<h2>Audia 0.2.0</h2>
<p>Audia 0.2.0 is a major alpha update focused on faster daily use, cleaner controls, better media handling, and stronger stability across mixer workflows.</p>
<h3>New and Improved</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Major redesign of Settings and menubar surfaces with cleaner structure and improved navigation.</li>
  <li>Compact and Advanced menu experiences with section reordering, visibility controls, and default-open behavior.</li>
  <li>Detached panel presentation with improved dismissal/position handling.</li>
  <li>Better onboarding flow with clearer feature walkthrough and browser-related setup guidance.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Mixer and Audio Controls</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Improved per-app and master control responsiveness with refined throttling and smoother UI updates.</li>
  <li>Better mute/zero-volume behavior to match native macOS expectations.</li>
  <li>Improved default-volume application behavior and stronger mute state consistency.</li>
  <li>Improved recording app visibility logic with grace-window handling for active audio sources.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Device Routing and Input</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Better output/input device control paths and reliability across app and global routing.</li>
  <li>Improved multi-device behavior in compact controls and safer option availability in unsupported scenarios.</li>
  <li>Input shortcut support improvements with better action handling and automation behavior.</li>
  <li>Auto-mute rule UX and settings improvements, including app selection/search refinements.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Media and Now Playing</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Expanded now-playing support and improved reliability when switching active media apps.</li>
  <li>Improved preferred-player behavior and automatic fallback handling when unavailable.</li>
  <li>Better transport/state controls with more consistent feedback in the UI.</li>
</ul>
<h3>HUD and Visual Feedback</h3>
<ul>
  <li>New custom HUD refinements with improved icon resolution and device-aware visuals.</li>
  <li>Better app/device icon handling across Bluetooth, built-in, and external device scenarios.</li>
  <li>Improved large-value rendering, quantization behavior, and style previews.</li>
  <li>Multiple visual polish updates for alignment, spacing, hit-testing, and animation quality.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Shortcuts and App Intents</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Expanded App Intents and shortcut controls for key audio actions.</li>
  <li>Better parameter handling and intent consistency for slider-based controls.</li>
  <li>Reliability fixes for intent-triggered actions and settings sync behavior.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Stability and Reliability</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Broad performance and responsiveness improvements across mixer and panel interactions.</li>
  <li>Fixes for panel resize flicker and close/dismiss edge cases.</li>
  <li>Reliability updates for launch/focus behavior and window presentation flow.</li>
  <li>Additional hardening for edge cases in core UI interactions.</li>
</ul>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/Bibhav48/audia-dist/releases/download/v0.2.0/Audia-0.2.0.zip"
                       sparkle:version="9"
                       sparkle:shortVersionString="0.2.0"
                       length="16319720"
                       type="application/octet-stream"
                       sparkle:edSignature="UCUilFfKJY22yXFRvKh1rX/74xfglhXvzASjXspv8mHixHceoqeIn5Zt3kdqDVIuKY+HDZn+IyOeSSHUCpeEAw==" />
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
